purecostumes.com 2017-12-26

# Privacy Policy - PureCostumes.com

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make links available to it on our homepage and at points where personal information may be requested. 

#### Information Collected

**Personal Information**  
PureCostumes.com collects personal Information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. “Personal Information” may include your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, mobile device number, birth date, and other purchasing information. You may also provide us with photographs or other video/media content which may contain Personal Information. Unless specifically stated, we do not require this information to obtain access to our site. By using our site and providing us with Personal Information, you consent to PureCostumes.com use of such information as described in this Privacy Policy. The Personal information we collect is used by PureCostumes.com for the purposes enumerated below and on our website: 

_Consumer Purchases_  
You may be asked to voluntarily provide personal information to make purchases or to have access to some features of our site. We use your Personal Information to process your orders and administer your account. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, but this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain products or services. When you make a purchase with PureCostumes.com, you are automatically registered for our email-marketing program, described below. 

_Customer Service_  
On some pages our visitors can submit comments or ask questions. We also collect Personal Information when you send us emails containing questions or requests. We only save Personal Information associated with questions and requests in our customer service database (unless otherwise stated herein, data which does not expire and is retained) in order to respond to those questions and requests, and to better serve you when responding to any questions or requests you may have in the future. 

_Emails_  
Some of our pages allow visitors to register to receive periodic emails from us. Any email you receive from PureCostumes.com will allow you to “unsubscribe” from this informational service at any time. 

_Accounts_  
When you register with us, PureCostumes.com collects some Personal Information in order to save preferences and segment information. On occasion, we may use this information to offer products or information that we think may be of interest to our customers (most of our customers enjoy receiving such material). 

Additionally, we may use this information to send emails reminding you of new products or special promotions. In addition, we may send you content-specific emails or special information about other PureCostumes.com products in the future. On occasion, we also may send information or offers to our email subscribers on behalf of other PureCostumes.com entities, such as other retail sites. If you prefer not to receive the information simply follow instructions in the email to unsubscribe 

_Email a Friend_  
There are some features on our website that may require visitors to enter another person’s Personal Information and/or email address in order to use the feature. We only use this information to allow visitors to share certain website content with friends. 

_Social Comments and Reviews_  
Our website may offer social comments and reviews opportunities, chat pages and other public engagement features in which you may provide Personal Information, materials and related content. If you submit Personal Information when using these public features, please note that such Personal Information may be publicly posted and otherwise disclosed and used without limitation or restriction. 

_Offers, Surveys and Promotions_  
PureCostumes.com may use your Personal Information to notify you about special offers, promotions, news and surveys that may be of interest to you. These notifications will be sent via email only. You may opt-out of receiving these notifications at any time by following the instructions set forth below in the Opt-Out section of this Privacy Policy or as set forth by following the instructions in the notification. 

_Legal Requirements_  
PureCostumes.com may have to disclose your Personal Information to provide Internet security or to comply with legal requirements. 

**Non-personal Information**  
PureCostumes.com collects a variety of non-personal information (“Anonymous Information” ) from visitors to our website. Anonymous Information may include: the operating system on your computer, the type of web browser you are using, your IP address, and the links you followed to enter and leave the site. Anonymous Information is not personally identifiable and is collected automatically via the use of cookies (small computer files saved on your hard drive) and other standard web technology by PureCostumes.com or a third party advertiser. Cookies allow us to tailor the website to better match your interests and preferences. With most internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the website may be limited and you may not be able to take advantage of many of our website’s features. We may use third party advertising companies to place ads on the website and to place our ads on other websites. These companies may use Anonymous Information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements on the website and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

PureCostumes.com web servers collect the domain names of visitors to our website, however, they do not recognize individual email addresses. Aggregate information showing the IP addresses and/or domain names of visitors, the number of visits, average time spent on the website, pages viewed, etc. is collected and used only for internal review to measure the overall use of our website and provide direction for its continuous improvement. This information is not sold to or shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

_Health Information_  
PureCostumes.com is not intended to or designed to solicit personal health information. We do not collect personal health information. 

#### Sharing of Information

Except as set forth in this Policy, we do not share your Personal Information unless you have given us permission to do so, for example, by checking the box allowing us to share your Personal Information with our marketing partners. 

PureCostumes.com may also disclose personally identifiable information based on a good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to conform to or comply with the law or that such disclosure is necessary to protect our website visitors or the general public. 

#### Privacy Of Children

PureCostumes.com encourages parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children’s online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 18, PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY WITH A PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 13, YOU SHOULD GET YOUR PARENT’S OR LEGAL GUARDIAN’S PERMISSION BEFORE GIVING OUT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION. Only visitors who are 18 years or older may purchase products from our website. 

#### Retention Of Information

PureCostumes.com retains Personal and Anonymous Information for as long as the information is relevant to our business purposes or in the case of Personal Information, until you request the removal of such information by contacting us as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

_Our Commitment to Data Security_  
PureCostumes.com utilizes appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to guard our online visitors’ Personal Information against unauthorized access and use, including Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology to protect credit card data transmission during online store purchases. All Personal Information is stored on secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled and all information is protected by PureCostumes.com security measures, which are periodically reviewed. 

_Links_  
PureCostumes.com may contain links to other sites, and we make every effort to only link to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. PureCostumes.com is not responsible for the collection or use of your Personal or Anonymous Information at any third party sites. Therefore, PureCostumes.com disclaims any liability for any third party’s use of your Personal or Anonymous Information obtained through using the third party website. 

_How You Can Access, Correct or Delete Your Personal Information_  
Visitors may modify Personal Information stored by PureCostumes.com by accessing their account. Stored Personal Information does not expire and is retained until you request that it be deleted from our database. If you would like to remove your name and Personal Information from our records, please email or us. 

_Email Communications_  
When you send an email to PureCostumes.com, you are communicating with us electronically. You thereby consent to receive communications from PureCostumes.com electronically. PureCostumes.com may communicate with you by email or by posting notices on the website. All agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that PureCostumes.com provides to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing. 

_Opt-Out_  
You can opt-out of use of this website or unsubscribe from receiving emails from us by following the instructions on any emails that you receive from us. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
Beginning January 1, 2005, California law permits individuals who are California residents to request once in any calendar year certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us by email at admin@purecostumes.com. 

**Questions/Contact Us**  
If you have questions about the website, the collection of information that occurs on the website, or this Privacy Policy, please email admin@purecostumes.com 

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
PureCostumes.com reserves the right to change, modify, add to or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes.
